look my [ __ ] all bad my [ __ ] all
real I ride in dick and some big tall
Hills big fat checks big large bills run
out flip like 10 car wheels cold ass
[ __ ] I give R Sho tend it for looks and
my look so cute I K them in the mouth I
feel all grills heat in the car that's
smell some Wheels I was born of fesh
diamonds on my neck I like board and
jets I like morning than sex but nothing
in this world that I like more than
checks
all I really want to see is the I don't
really need all a bad [ __ ] need is I
got in the busting the I got in the
touch me I'll sh shake ass you get a
little bag and take it to the store get
a little cash you shake it real fast you
get a little more I got in the C out the
I got B in the C not the I got to fly I
need jet [ __ ] I need room for my legs I
got a baby I need some money I need tee
for my egg all y [ __ ] in trouble bre
Knuckles to scuffle I heard that c went
pop yeah I go pop that's me buting
Bubble I'm the with the drip baby mommy
with the clip walkies with a [ __ ] bring
a to the Whip and she find she godamn
fing pass the mirror damn I'm fine let a
[ __ ] try me hmer time
[Music]
I was born to flex diamonds on my neck I
like board and jets I like morning sex
but nothing in this world that I like
more than check all I really want to see
is the I don't really need a d all a bad
[ __ ] need is I got B in the C busting
not the RO I got B in the C
touch
me shake a little ass you get a little
bag and take it to the store get a
little cash you shake a fast a little
more I got
the the I got in the touch me I'll shoot
[ __ ] pop your pop [ __ ] pop whoever you
know who pop the most [ __ ] the people sh
not together you know that cardio freak
all my pajamas is Lea [ __ ] I black on
your ass
forever like a honey spit like a tumm
come get
mommy top [ __ ] Kiss the Ring and kick
rockis drum it down back it up make that
[ __ ] put I like my [ __ ] dark like going
to eat this like I was born to flex
diamonds on my neck I like Bo and jets I
like more than sex but nothing in this
world that I like more than C all I
really want to see is the I don't really
need a d all a bad [ __ ] need us k k c
money
Mone
moneyy money
[Music]